William R. Cotter Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Executive Records, 1971-1981
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 766)
  - Justice, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 767)
  - Labor, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 767)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 768)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 769)
  - Postal Service, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 770)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 771)
  - Selective Service, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 772)
  - Small Business Administration, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 773)
  - Social Security Administration, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 774)
  - State Department
    - General, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 775)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1971 January - June (Box 43:, Folder 776)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1971 July - December (Box 43:, Folder 777)
    - Jewish “Show” Trials, U.S.S.R., 1971 (Box 43:, Folder 778)
  - Transportation, 1971 (Box 43:, Folder 779)
  - Treasury, 1971 (Box 43:, Folder 780)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1971 (Box 43:, Folder 781)
  - Agriculture, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 782)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 783)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 784)
  - Civil Rights Commission, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 785)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 786)
  - Commerce, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 787)
  - Cost of Living Council, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 788)
  - Budget/Office of Budget, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 789)
  - Defense
    - General, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 790)
    - Air Force, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 791)
    - Army, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 792)
    - Coast Guard, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 793)
    - Navy, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 794)
  - Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 795)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 796)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 797)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 798)
  - Federal Power Commission
    - General, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 799)
    - Newington Power Failures, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 800)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 801)
  - Federal Maritime Commission, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 802)
  - General Services Administration>, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 803)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - General (Box 44:, Folder 804)
    - Hill Burton Funds (Eligibility Regulations), 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 805)
    - Connecticut Tumor Registry, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 806)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 807)
  - Department of the Interior, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 808)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 809)
  - Justice, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 810)
  - Labor, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 811)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 812)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 813)
  - Postal Service, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 814)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 815)
  - Selective Service, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 816)
  - Small Business Administration, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 817)
  - Social Security Administration, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 818)
  - State Department
    - General, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 819)
    - Haiti, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 820)
    - Armenian Martyr Day, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 821)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1972 January - April (Box 44:, Folder 822)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1972 June (Box 44:, Folder 823)
  - Transportation, 1972
    - General, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 824)
    - East Hartford Highways, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 825)
  - Connecticut, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 826)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 827)
  - Agriculture, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 828)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 829)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 830)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 831)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 832)
  - Commerce
    - General, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 833)
    - Anti-Israel Boycotts (Joseph Dubitzky), 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 834)
  - Cost of Living Council
    - General, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 835)
    - Inflated Food Costs and Meat Boycott, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 836)
  - Defense
    - General, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 837)
    - Air Force, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 838)
    - Army, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 839)
    - Coast Guard, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 840)
    - Navy, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 841)
  - Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 842)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 843)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 844)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 845)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 846)
  - Federal Energy Administration, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 847)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 848)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 849)
  - General Services Administration, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 850)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 851)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 852)
  - Department of the Interior, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 853)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 854)
  - Justice, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 855)
  - Labor
    - General, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 856)
    - Manpower Programs, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 857)
    - R.C./O.S.H.A., 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 858)
    - Puerto Rican Veterans, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 859)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 860)
  - Postal Service, 1973 (Box 45:, Folder 861)
  - Office of the President
    - General, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 862)
    - Office of Energy and Policy: Gas Shortage, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 863)
    - OEO Budget Cut, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 864)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 865)
  - Small Business Administration, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 866)
  - Social Security Administration, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 867)
  - State Department
    - General, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 868)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict: Cambodian Bombing, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 869)
    - Middle East Crisis, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 870)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1973 January 3 - 9 (Box 46:, Folder 871)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1973 January 10 - 15 (Box 46:, Folder 872)
    - Southeast Asia, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 873)
    - 200-Mile Limit, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 874)
  - Tariff Commission, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 875)
  - Transportation
    - General, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 876)
    - Alaska Pipeline, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 877)
    - Amtrak, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 878)
  - Treasury, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 879)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1973 (Box 46:, Folder 880)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 881)
  - Agriculture, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 882)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 883)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 884)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 885)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 886)
  - Civil Rights Commission
    - General, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 887-888)
  - Commerce, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 889)
  - Consumer Product Safety, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 890)
  - Cost of Living Council, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 891)
  - Defense
    - General, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 892)
    - Army, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 893)
    - Coast Guard, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 894)
    - Navy, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 895)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 896)
  - Export-Import Bank, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 897)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 898)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 899)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 900)
  - Defense: Air Force, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 901)
  - Federal Energy Administration, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 902)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 903)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 904)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 905)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 906)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 907)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 908)
  - General Services Administration, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 909)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 910)
  - Office of Education, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 911)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 912)
  - Department of the Interior, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 913)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 914)
  - Labor, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 915)
  - Management and Budget, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 916)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 917)
  - Postal Service, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 918)
  - Office of the President
    - Office of Energy and Policy, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 919)
  - Small Business Administration, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 920)
  - State Department
    - General, 1974 (Box 47:, Folder 921)
    - Southeast Asian Conflict, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 922)
    - Middle East Crisis, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 923)
    - Cults/Lebanon, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 924)
  - Tariff Commission, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 925)
  - Transportation, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 926)
  - Treasury, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 927)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1974 (Box 48:, Folder 928)
  - Connecticut, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 929)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 930)
  - Agriculture, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 931)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 932)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 933)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 934)
  - Cost of Living Council, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 935)
  - Defense
    - General, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 936)
    - Air Force, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 937)
    - Army, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 938)
    - Army Birds, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 939)
    - Navy, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 940)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 941)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 942)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 943)
  - Social Security Administration
    - Sarah Katz, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 944)
    - Nursing Salary Cost, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 945)
  - State Department, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 946)
  - Transportation
    - General, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 947)
    - Amtrak, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 948)
    - D.O.T.: Coast Guard, Railroad Bridge, Old Lyme, Old Saybrook, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 949)
  - Treasury, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 950)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1975 (Box 48:, Folder 951)
  - Connecticut, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 952)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 953)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 954)
  - Agriculture, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 955)
  - WIC in Connecticut, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 956)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 957)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 958)
  - Commerce, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 959)
  - Defense
    - General, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 960)
    - Army, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 961)
    - Army, Moe, Hilda G.: Glastonbury dump, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 962)
    - Navy, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 963)
  - Energy Research and Development, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 964)
  - Windsor/Combustion Engineering, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 965)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 966)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 967)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 968)
  - Federal Energy Administration
    - General, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 969)
    - Governor Grasso: CT Natural Gas Prices, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 970)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 971)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 972)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 972)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 974)
  - General Services Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 975)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - General, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 976)
    - Jonathan May, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 977)
    - Lynne Mahanne, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 978)
    - Office of Education, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 979)
    - Easter Seal, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 980)
    - Association of Operating Room Technicians, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 981)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD)
    - General, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 982)
    - Brooke Amendment: CT Welfare Housing, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 983)
  - Department of the Interior, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 984)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 985)
  - Justice, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 986)
  - Labor
    - General, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 987)
    - Manpower Programs, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 988)
    - OSHA, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 989)
  - National Aeronautics & Science Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 990)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 991)
  - Postal Service, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 992)
  - Office of the President, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 993)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 994)
  - Selective Service, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 995)
  - Small Business Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 996)
  - Social Security Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 997)
  - Health, Education and Welfare: Quarterly Payments to the Social Security Administration, 1976 (Box 49:, Folder 998)
  - State Department, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 999)
  - Transportation
    - General, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1000)
    - Conrail, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1001)
    - N.E. Corridor: Design and Construction Work, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1002)
    - Amtrak, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1003)
    - Griffin Line (Bills) Conrail, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1004)
  - Customs: Edward S. Stolarz, Commercial Fishing Supplies, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1005)
  - Taxes: U.S. and CT Offices, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1006)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1976 (Box 50:, Folder 1007)
  - Miscellaneous: Connecticut, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1008)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1009)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1010)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1011)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1012)
  - Commerce
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1013)
    - Economic Development Association, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1014)
  - Civil Service Administration: OPS Hearings on Opening of CSA, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1015)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) Grant Application
    - Dennis Rezendes, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1016)
    - Development and Investment Program, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1017)
  - Hartford Chamber of Commerce GAO: Harris Thomas, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1018)
  - Community Product Safety Commission, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1019)
  - Defense
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1020)
    - Army, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1021)
    - Air Force, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1022)
    - Army Corp: Church of the Good Shepard, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1023)
    - Navy, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1024)
    - Civil Preparedness, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1025)
  - Energy Research and Development
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1026)
    - Choice-Vend. Inc. (Maxmiller), 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1027)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1028)
    - Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant Information, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1029)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1030)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1031)
  - FEA and Department of Energy, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1032)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1033)
  - Federal Power Commission
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1034)
    - Northeast Utilities and Boston MDC, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1035)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1036)
  - Federal Trade Commission
    - General, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1037)
    - Health Food Issue, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1038)
    - Proposal for Used Car Window Stickers, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1039)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1977 (Box 50:, Folder 1040)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1041)
  - General Services Administration, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1042)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - Social Security Administration, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1043)
    - Welfare Reform, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1044)
    - Office of Education, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1045)
    - Civil Rights Forms: John H. Conrad, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1046)
  - Home Loan Bank Board, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1047)
  - Government Printing Office, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1048)
  - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1049)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1050)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1051)
  - Miscellaneous
    - All other federal agencies, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1052)
    - United Technologies Files, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1053)
    - Governors Council on Voluntary Action, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1054)
    - Veterinary School in CT, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1055)
    - Phelps-Gaylord Hospital, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1056)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - Johathan May, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1057)
    - Hartford Board of Education (Title VII), 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1058)
  - Housing and Urban Development
    - General, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1059)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1060)
    - Flood Insurance Program, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1061)
  - Department of the Interior, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1062)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - REA Express Bankruptcy Case, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1063)
  - Justice
    - General, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1064)
    - INS, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1065)
  - Labor
    - General, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1066)
    - CETA, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1067)
    - Nick Carbone, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1068)
    - LMSA (ERISA), 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1069)
  - Management and Budget, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1070)
  - Postal Service, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1071)
  - Office of the President, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1072)
  - Securities & Exchange Commission, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1073)
  - Small Business Administration, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1074)
  - State: Israel, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1075)
  - Transportation
    - General, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1076)
    - UMTA, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1077)
    - Amtrak, 1977 (Box 51:, Folder 1078)
    - DOT: East Hartford Traffic Relating to I-84, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1079)
  - Treasury
    - General, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1080)
    - IRS, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1081)
    - John Herr, Investment Annuity (IRS), 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1082)
    - W. Lewis Hyde, Tuition Remission Taxation, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1083)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1977 (Box 52:, Folder 1084)
  - Agriculture
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1085)
    - Forest Service, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1086)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1087)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1088)
  - Commerce, 1978
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1089)
    - Census Bureau, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1090)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1091)
    - Federal Maritime Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1092)
    - Stratford Weather Station, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1093)
    - SMSA Proposal, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1094)
  - Community Service Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1095)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1096)
  - Defense
    - U.S. Marine Corps, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1097)
    - Navy, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1098)
    - F-14, F-18 Aircraft, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1099)
    - Air Force, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1100)
    - Army, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1101)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA): Water Containment Control, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1102)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1103)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1104)
  - Office of the President
    - Office of Management & Budget, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1105)
    - General, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1106)
    - Council on Wage & Price Stability, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1107)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1108)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1109)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1110)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1111)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1112)
  - General Services Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1113)
  - Department of Energy, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1114)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1115)
    - Health, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1116)
    - General, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1117)
    - Social Security Administration, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1118)
    - Education, 1978 (Box 52:, Folder 1119)
    - Welfare, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1120)
  - Housing and Urban Development
    - General, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1121)
    - Flood Insurance Program, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1122)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1123)
  - Department of the Interior
    - General, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1124)
    - National Park Service, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1125)
    - International Trade Commission, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1126)
  - Justice
    - Danbury Prison Fire, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1127)
    - Law Enforcement Assts. Administration, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1128)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1129)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1130)
    - CETA, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1131)
  - Labor, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1132)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1133)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1134)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1135)
  - National Science Foundation, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1136)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1137)
  - Small Business Administration, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1138)
  - State
    - General, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1139)
    - Passport and Visa, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1140)
    - International Whaling Commission, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1141)
  - Transportation
    - Federal Railroad Administration, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1142)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1143)
    - U.S. Coast Guard, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1144)
    - Conrail, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1145)
    - Rocky Hill Spur Line, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1146)
    - Delaware and Hudson Bankruptcy, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1147)
    - Conrail Proposed Abandonments, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1148)
    - New England Rail Study, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1149)
    - Amtrak, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1150)
  - Treasury
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1151)
    - U.S. Customs Service, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1152)
    - IRS, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1153)
  - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1154)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1155)
  - U.S. Parole Commission, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1156)
  - Postal Service
    - Lamsden, Arthur J., 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1157)
    - Fishman and Sons, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1158)
  - U.S. Railroad Retirement Board, 1978 (Box 53:, Folder 1159)
  - Miscellaneous Agencies, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1160)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1161)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1162)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1163)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1164)
  - Commerce
    - Census Bureau, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1165)
    - Economic Development Administration (Box 54:, Folder 1166)